# **Natan Dolny**

Q London, UK

natandolny@gmail.com

(+44) 07 413 156 793

in In/natan-dolny

Portfolio: <a href="https://natandolny.github.io/Portfolio/">https://natandolny.github.io/Portfolio/</a>

## Summary:

Recent BSc Games Technology (Second Class, Upper Division) graduate, experienced in Unity and Unreal game engines. Specialise in C# and C++ programming languages with further Python experience. Proficient with Visual Studio, Autodesk Maya and Adobe Suite. Professional in the use of online repositories, version control and merge tools such as GitHub and GitKraken. Also, experienced in communication tools like Slack and have worked with office tools for over 5 years. Deeply interested in the creation of AI, world-building, and game immersion systems. Seasoned in high-pressure and fast-paced work environments. Well-versed in physics, engineering, mathematics, (including but not limited to algebra and statistics) and problem-solving.

## Skills:

## Programming Languages:

C# and C++ - 5 years. Used in IDEs for Unity 3D and Unreal. Educated in Object Oriented Programming.

Python – 1 year.

# Game Engines:

Unity 3D and Unreal Engine—3 years. Developed games, developer tools, systems, AI, lighting, special effects, audio systems, animations and animators, level design, scripting, camera controls and cutscenes, player controllers, and player mechanics including abilities.

Repositories, Version Control and Merge Tools: GitHub – 3 years. GitHub Desktop, GitKraken and Terminal – 3 years.

## Developer Programs:

Visual Studio/CLion - 5 years.

**Autodesk Maya.** Animations, lighting, level design, texture mapping, and 3D asset creation for game engine use. **Adobe Suite.** Premiere Pro, Photoshop, Audition, After Effects.

#### Office-Related Tools:

Microsoft Office and Google Counterparts – 5 years. Video Conferencing – 5 years. Teams, Meet, Zoom. Cloud Storage – 5 years. OneDrive, Google Drive etc. Project Management. Trello, Gantt Charts, etc. Communication Tools. Slack, Discord, etc.

Languages:

English and Polish – Native level.

## Education:

Bachelor of Science in Games Technology | University of the West of England Second Class (Upper Division)

Sep 2017 – Jul 2020

Sep 2020 - Jul 2023

Computer Science, Maths, Physics, Engineering | Hereford Sixth Form College

## Experience:

#### English Tutoring (Self-Employed)

Jan 2022 to Mar 2022

English tutored foreigners. Adept in diverse teaching methods and developed a personal approach to increase lesson engagement and fulfilment. Used social media and Google Meets for advertisement or scheduling. Designed lessons for various abilities.

## Primark, Widemarsh Street, Hereford

Aug 2018 to Sep 2020

Being a retail assistant brought many unique challenges, always adapting to the store's needs was a must. Regularly used my multilingual skills to assist others. Was trained in customer service and communication equipment. Developed interpersonal skills and became proficient at operating the till counter, tidying and stock handling.

## University Projects:

**Cohort Project** – Part of a 6-month, 35-person project that emulated a development studio. Developed a PC and PS5 game in Unity, using Agile Development methodology. Frequently used tools like Trello, Slack and Discord to document, plan, and communicate with the cohort. Personally developed back-end systems revolving around data and event triggers. Transitioned to player experience, improving the UI and menus, e.g. transparency effects for interacted objects. Collaborated with 4-8 person groups to communicate changes and make improvements. Performed presentations to showcase progress and receive feedback.

**Group Development** – Took part in multiple group-oriented (4-8 people) game development tasks and game jams. Additionally, designed a board game in a group of 6, taking on a leadership role. Partook in the official Global Games Jam (2023).

References are available on request.